Sotomayor Torrealba **Manuel Jose**

+58414-0539599 +58244-6635392

SPANISH ENGLISH

```
Backend programation
Frontend programation

Server
Networking
mobile programation

● ● ● ● ● ● ○ ○ ○ ○
```

сто •••••• Python

Python
Fedora
GIT
AngularJs
PHP
Jquery
HTML5
CSS3
RabbitMQ
Postgresql
Mysql

Mysql Command AT

API REST

Node|s

Socketio

Nginx Android

About Me

a responsible, competitive person who loves to learn new things every day, I he several projects like Fullstack and like a project manager, I am good like trammer using the next tecnologies: Angularjs, node, is, socket.io, python, djang old studio, php, wordpress, jquery. C #, I have extensive knowledge in managir servers, and administering services.

I use GIT like the repositories control tool, I have experience carrying out projects of automation with MQTT, AMOP protocols and handling equipment such as Arduinos, raspberry pl and modules like NFC, RIPO, Wireless, Beacon, management queuing sy using RabbitMQ, I have worked with sqlite, posgressol, sqlserver, mysql, etc. maybe I have used other technologies but those are the more importan.

Education

formatic Engineer graduated from La universidad Politecnica Territorial de Araqua la Vic-ring my time at the university, i made three (3) projects, which consisted in the velopment of an inventory system for INCE located in La Victoria (1 year); also i de-monitoring system on IVECO factory in the same city (2 years). Both were develope ing the next tecnologies: php (code)ginater), juguery, htmlfs and csai, (2009-2014)

Experience

Collecworld (from 2014-1 to 2014-6)

sales, etc. began to develop in codeigniter, then he went on to pytho Collectworld.com. year 2014, duration: 6 months, position: fullstack programmer tools: django, codeignater, jquery, postgresql, bootstrat, GIT, wind: Trello, slack, paache, basecamp

OmegaSoft (from 2014-6 to 2014-12)

This system was basically replicate http://arandasoft.com/ in its own web syst with improvements, using new technologies for remote communication and his ticker, if developed in a company called OMEGASCPT.com programmer tools: django, jquery, postgresqi, bootstrat, GT, debian

SocialMedios (from 2014-12 to 2016-2)

Basically, this system generated analitys about what the user wants and offers to the client the best option, the information was generated by others modules like the inventory, marketing and store that the user used, this studied help to the owns store to take better desilton to improve his business

year 2015, duration: 4 months, position: backend programmer and product manager tools: diapo, mysql, draw.io, documentacion, scrum, GIT, fedo productive, nginx

n Development ith freepbx, this system generated calls to the client since the web to ow dynamic question to employees that then they have to make to l, this answers are saved and generated analitys

year 2015, duration: Z. months, position: backend grogrammer and product manager tools: django, mysel, freepbx, angularjs, redes, scrum, GIT, fedora, nginx, productive, growth of the control of the con

Squares and found and synchromanum connection with the connection (which with electronic engineers) year 2015, duration: 6 months, position: backed programmer and product manager tools: django, mysql, freepbx, angularjs, networking, scrum, GIT, fedora nginx, productive, drawlio, command AT, beacon, vifi, Ite, gps, memcached, mgtt, amgtt, rabbit, celery, VPN, RFID, NFC, sqlite, celery, raspbian sarrollo de Sistema de Almacen (fulfilliment, foroshipping) it developed a storage system where packets are received, stored, they are verified and QIR of each packet is generated, they could create new stores whether and sistes, product information that was obtained in each

handlers by hashtag, with more than 250 followers and by the san generated a link that redirects to a landing page. year 2016, duration: 2 months, position: backend programmer and product manager tools: django, mysql, scrum, GIT, fedora, nginx, script dji

Abaco System (from 2016-3 to today)

year 2016, Duration: 4 months, position: CTO, backend and frontend programmer tools: django, mysql, angularjs, scrum, GIT, fedora nginx, productive, draw.lo, script django, celery II System Development

makes calls to customers with messages generated by a Loquendo tts re uploaded by the user, each time a call was made, it generated d call credits available year 2016, duration: 2 months, position: backend programmer and product manager tools: django, mysql, asterisk, angularjs, scrum, GIT, fedora nginx, productive, draw.io, script django, loquendo

ification System ly it is a system wit ding push notification ush. Abaco System android application developed using firebase as a platform nd database in real time, with a web platform where you can

year 2016, duration: I months, position: fullstack programmer, CTO, movil tools: django, mysql, angularjs, scrum, GIT, ubuntu, ngi script django, android estudio

rear 2016, duration: 1 mes, position: wordpress programmer pool: workpress

SoluctionBET (from 2016-4 to 2016-7) use several casinos endpoint service to work as a kind of anged for real money depending on the type of currency. soluction BE

happyhourcasino.com soluction BET year 2016, duration: 3 months, position: fullstack programmer tools: django, mysql, jquery, Angularjs, GIT, Ubur JSON, End point proveedores

LibreTaxi (from 2016-6 to today)

year 2016, duration: 3 months, position: backend programmer, CTO, mobile tools: django, mysql, angularjs, scrum, GIT, Ubuntu nginx, productive, drawie, script django